All right. In this video, we're going to
take this Princess Bride quote and we're
going to adjust it to apply more to us.
So, the Princess Bride quote says,
"Don't rush me, Sunny. You rush a
miracle man, you get Ron Miracles."
Sorry, I can't do voices. All right.
What we're going to do is we are going
to replace some of the text to make it
apply more to us. So, we're going to
take this movie quote and we're going to
replace Miracle Man with programmer
because that's what you are. All right.
So we'll say let um new quote. So we're
creating a new variable. It's called new
quote and we're setting it equal to the
movie quote except we're going to use
replace. So we'll sayreplace
and then this takes in two pieces of
information. The thing we want to
replace and what we want to replace it
with. So we want to replace the text
miracle man with the text
programmer.
So, we'll save this and then let's just
alert our new quote so we can see what
it looks like.
So, we'll save it. We'll come over to
our web browser and it says, "Don't rush
me, Sunny. You rush a programmer, you
get rotten miracles." Um, and while
programmers do perform things that
people might consider miracles, it might
be better to replace the word miracles
with code. So, we could do this again.
We could say let new new quote equal new
quote dotreplace.
And we could then replace miracles in
the new quote with the text code. Or we
can do this all on one line, which is
how I prefer to do it. So I'm going to
say take the original movie quote,
replace miracle man with programmer.
Once you've done that, do dot and then
type replace again. And then now we're
going to say miracles.
and we're going to replace it with code.
So, what this does is it goes into our
movie quote, it replaces every
occurrence of Miracle Man with the word
programmer. And then it replaces um the
word miracles with the word code. So
now, if we save this and we come over to
our website
and we reload it, it says, "Don't rush
me, Sunny. You rush a programmer, you
get rotten code." And that concludes
this video. Thanks for watching.